复 仇 之 手
字幕:Dex7er  公众号:值得看的
Morning, Uncle Cash.
早上好 卡什叔叔
Some heavy reading for ninth grade.
九年级的重头读物
It's one of mom's old college books
这是妈妈大学时的一本旧书
by this British guy, Eric Padgett.
作者是英国人埃里克-帕吉特
He's like a philosopher, writes about ethics
他就像个哲学家 写了一些道德问题
and how to be good.
以及如何做个好人
So you're reading textbooks for fun?
所以你读教科书就是为了消遣
I guess.
我猜也是
Well, don't hurt yourself.
好了 别读累着了哦
Your dad up?
你爸爸起了吗
- Oh, what time is it? - Time to feed.
- 哦 几点了 - 喂食时间到了
- I'm going... - Come on.
- 我去  - 来吧
- I'm going. - Let's go.
- 我就去 - 走吧
All right, all right, all right.
好了 好了 好了
Mr. Bright-Eyes and Bushy-Tail,
大眼睛毛尾巴先生
just give me a minute.
给我点时间
We ain't got time for a Lamaze class.
我们可没时间做孕产期保健运动
Let's go! Come on, let's get on it.
我们走 来吧 开始干活了
We got some hungry hippos out here.
这里有一些饥饿的小马等着喂呢
Here, chick, chick, chick.
吃吧 小鸡 小鸡
No need to shove, there's enough for everybody.
不要抢 每个人都有足够的吃的
C'mon, little guy, let's go.
来吧 小家伙 我们走
In you get. All right. There you go.
进去吧 好了 去吧
Get!
开饭
Come on now.
来吧
Let's go.
吃吧
How's he doing?
它怎么样了
Been lappin' up that zinc for over a month now.
一个多月来 一直在舔锌
No reason he shouldn't be trying to breed
它没有理由不试着
with a heifer on the lot.
与这头母牛配种啊
Rachel would know.
瑞秋懂这个
It's like the damn thing talked to her.
好像那东西会跟她说话似的
Yeah.
是啊
Never said shit to me.
从没跟我说过一句
Yeah, me neither.
是啊 也没跟我说过
But I keep listening.
但我一直用心听着
You okay, girl?
你没事吧 姑娘
Dad!
爸爸
What the hell's got her running out here
发生了什么事让她跑这里来了
like the house is on fire?
像家里着火了一样
- What's going on, darling? - Come quick!
- 怎么了 亲爱的 - 快点过来
You all right?
你没事吧
It's coming!
生了
Hey. Hey, there she go.
嘿 嘿 她生了
Whoa, easy easy, easy.
哇 哇 放松 放松
Easy, girl.
别紧张 姑娘
Yeah, I'm not liking this.
是的 情况不妙
She's pushing hard.
她很用力
Yeah, and ain't nothing coming out.
是啊 可是什么也没出来
Whoa, whoa.
哇哦 哇哦
All right, mama, I'ma take a look,
好吧 妈妈 让我来看一下
make sure things are in order.
确保一切按部就班
Oh, yeah, I see the problem.
哦 好了 我知道问题在哪了
What's wrong?
怎么了
Foal's stuck. She's got one foot forward.
小马驹卡住了 它的一只脚朝前
Wanna get a vet?
要找兽医吗
Probably long gone, the time she get here.
等她来了 可能早就死了
You got 10 to 15 minutes in this state.
这种情况 你有10到15分钟的时间
And I say we on the tail end of that.
要我说 我们的时间不多了
- Oh, keep her still, Cash. - Whoa.
- 让她别动 卡什 - 哇哦
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇哦 哇哦 哇哦
- Easy, my girl. - I got her.
- 放松 我的女孩 - 我抓住她了
Pull the tail back.
把尾巴拉回去
Dad's trying to fix it.
爸爸正在救你
- Got it? - Hold on. Got the hoof!
- 找到了吗 - 等一下 抓住蹄子了
- All right. - Just gotta get the hoof, girl.
- 好吧 - 只要抓住蹄子就好了 姑娘
Easy, Flagen.
别紧张 弗拉根
- Step on back now, she got it. - Yeah.
- 现在退后吧 她能行 - 好的
She got it.
她能行
- There it is. - All right.
- 出来了 - 好了
She got it.
她搞定了
Yeah, she precious little thing.
是啊 这真是个小宝贝东西
Just think, most people still sleeping on a Sunday.
想想看 大多数人在周日还在睡懒觉呢
Sensible ones anyway.
很明智的人
- Their loss. - Yeah.
- 他们的损失 - 是啊
Welcome to the family.
欢迎加入我们的大家庭
Come on.
走吧
Savannah, let's go!
萨凡纳 我们走
- Gonna find it? - Yeah.
- 能找到吗 - 能
It gets lost now and again.
它三天两头就会走失了
Oh, you look beautiful, baby girl.
哦 你看起来真漂亮 宝贝女儿
- Thanks, Dad. - Yeah.
- 谢谢 爸爸 - 好
Why don't you come with us?
你为什么不跟我们一起
Oh, not really feeling too churchy these days.
哦 最近不太想去教堂了
'Sides, I need to get that tractor running.
还有 我得把拖拉机修好了
I've been saying I would for the last month.
上个月我就一直说要修的
Well...
嗯
come meet us for lunch at the grill.
来烤肉店吃午饭吧
Bringing out the big guns.
那你得出点血了
Do it for the patty melt.
那就烤肉奶酪三明治
Well... you buying?
那么 你买单吗
Hot and on the table when you walk in.
保证你一进门就热气腾腾地摆在桌上
All right, damn it. You got me.
好吧 该死 我去
Knew it would.
就知道会这样
Y'all have fun now.
祝你们玩得开心
Get that thing fixed then.
那就把它修好
Oh, I'm on it.
哦 我这就去
Well, we're just gonna keep asking him.
我们会继续邀请他的
He just misses Mom.
他只是想念妈妈
- Yeah. - I do, too.
- 是啊 - 我也是
She would have been proud of him this morning.
今天早上这事 她一定会为他感到骄傲的
Yeah, she would.
她会的
When I was a boy,
我小时候
my daddy would take me out hunting.
我爸爸会带我去打猎
We'd wake up before sunrise, traipse through the cold
我们会在日出前醒来 在寒冷和黑暗中穿行
and the dark, leaves crackling under our feet.
树叶在我们脚下噼啪作响
Some of you know what I am talking about.
你们有些人知道我在说什么
I see you nodding, Andy.
我看到你在点头 安迪
And look, I stand before you now a preacher.
听着 现在我作为一名传教士站在你们面前
I'm just a sinner, just like you.
我只是个罪人 和你们一样
Just like you.
就像你们一样
There was a time I was a real son of a bitch.
曾几何时 我真是个狗娘养的
Hell, you can look it up.
见鬼 你们可以查一查
They got a file on me down at the police station.
警察局里有我的档案
I know a little something about that.
我对此略知一二
All right. Not a word out of you, Sheriff.
好吧 你可什么都别说 警长
But I was in those same woods
但我也曾在那片树林里
that I'd go hunting with my old man.
和我父亲一起打猎
And I had a revelation and I realized
我得到了一个启示 我意识到
God is always there.
上帝总是在那里
He's always been there, listening, waiting, ready
他一直在那里 倾听着 等待着 准备着
to open his arms to us.
向我们张开双臂
- Amen. - Give me another amen.
- 阿门 - 再给我一声阿门
- Amen. - Thank you.
- 阿门 - 谢谢
'Preciate it.
非常感谢
Just wonderful, Pastor.
真是太好了 牧师
Appreciate you taking the time.
感谢您抽出时间
I wouldn't miss it.
我不会错过的
Beautiful way to start the morning.
开启一天的美好方式
- All right. - Sheriff.
- 好的 - 警长
Well, the Lord is quicker to forgive than your fellow man.
好吧 上帝会比你的同伴更快原谅你
How's Finney holding up?
芬尼怎么样了
Touch and go.
很难说
You need to get him off that Memphis Blind.
你得让他从那坏习惯中走出来
Is he hunting?
他还打猎吗
Not hardly.
几乎不去
Well, it's worse than I thought.
嗯 比我想象的还要糟糕
- Yeah. - How about you, Savannah?
- 嗯 - 你呢 萨凡纳
Has your uncle taken you hunting yet this season?
这个季节你叔叔带你去打猎了吗
We have, but all I get is skunked.
我们有 但我打到的都是 臭鼬
That's not true. You've been close on a couple.
不是这样的 有几次你已经差点就成功了
Go on, show him what you picked out.
来 给他看看你挑的东西
What you got?
是什么
Oh, that is some prime cutting steel. Look at that.
哦 这可是上等的切割钢材 看看这个
Reckon she's got about, what, six months of morning chores
我估计她大概有六个月的家务事要做吧
before you pay it off.
在你还清之前
Oh, your uncle's a prickly bastard, isn't he?
哦 你叔叔是个棘手的混蛋 不是吗
A miser, too.
也是个守财奴
Now this one's got you figured, Cash.
这孩子看你看的很准啊 卡什
Yeah, she's a regular Dr. Phil.
是啊 她是个标准的心理专家
I'll tell you what,
我来告诉你
I'm gonna be eating your dad's patty melt
我要吃了给你爸爸的烤肉奶酪三明治
if he don't make it here soon.
如果他还不尽快出现的话
You should.
你应该
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
Finney, where the hell are you?
芬尼 你到底在哪
Twelve-dollar burger's getting cold.
What's this now?
这又是干什么
Cash. Didn't think you'd mind.
卡什 没想到你会介意
Doe here is just having a little bite to eat.
杜伊过来就是吃两口
Might lose my appetite looking at that hand though.
不过 看着那只手 我可能会没胃口
Mm.
嗯
Get up. Let her out.
起来 让她出去
You left her all alone.
你丢下她一个人
We were just being polite, keeping her company.
我们只是出于礼貌才陪着她
Come on, Savannah.
走吧 萨凡纳
Fly away, little butterfly.
飞走吧 小蝴蝶
We just wanna have a chat with your uncle.
我们只是想和你叔叔聊一聊
Come here, sweetheart.
过来 亲爱的
Go get a dessert at the bar.
去吧台吃点甜点
I won't be long. It's all right. Don't worry.
我不会太久的 没事 别担心
Sit down.
坐下
What do you want?
你想要什么
We don't want nothing. Big Cat does.
我们什么都不想要 大猫要
I got nothing to say to Big Cat.
我跟大猫没什么好说的
Big Cat got something to say to you.
大猫有话要跟你说
About your farm.
关于你农场的
About my farm? What about it?
关于我的农场 怎么了
All right, come on.
好吧 来吧
♪ Oh, God I don't understand it ♪
哦 上帝 我不明白
♪ You're always playing To disown on me ♪
你总是玩弄我 想要抛弃我
♪ I got sucker punched, Get me... ♪
我吃了一记重拳 让我
There she is.
她来了
There's my girl. Church good?
我的女儿 教会还好吗
I thought you were coming to lunch.
我以为你会来吃午饭
Oh, I'm sorry, kiddo.
哦 对不起 孩子
Savannah, give me a minute with your pops, will ya?
萨凡纳 给我和你爸爸一分钟时间 好吗
Go on, darling. Let me talk to Cash.
去吧 亲爱的 让我跟卡什谈谈
I'ma make another one.
我要再来一杯
Now, you let me know if you have a change of heart.
现在 如果你改变主意了 请告诉我
This you being funny?
你在搞笑吗
Are you really trying to fuck with my sobriety?
你真的想让我破了酒戒吗
You still smoke.
你还在抽烟啊
And that's some nasty-ass shit, let me tell you.
让我告诉你 那也是一坨恶心的屎
Oh...
哦
this you being an asshole.
你又开始混蛋了
Mm, I'm just saying.
我只是说说
You can throw them back as good as anyone.
你也可以像其他人一样回击啊
I was a drunken dumbass,
说我是个醉醺醺的笨蛋
now, you're throwing 'em back for both of us.
现在 你说的不就是我们俩嘛
Now that... that is a truth you won't hear on the radio.
这 这是你在收音机里听不到的事实
See, you missed lunch.
看 你错过了午餐
The Buck and Doe joined us at the diner today.
巴克和杜伊今天我们吃饭的时候过来了
They're under the impression that you're in Big Cat's debt.
他们话里话外地暗示你欠了大猫的债
That you owe.
你借的
Let me tell you something about this farm, Cash.
我跟你说说这个农场吧 卡什
Like a bucket with a hole in it.
就像一个有洞的水桶
Did you give the note on my sister's place to Big Cat?
你把我姐姐的地方抵押给大猫了吗
I took a loan on my place.
我拿自己的地方贷了点款
I had to, or this farm would be gone any damn way.
我没办法 不然这个农场无论如何都保不住了
Goddammit!
真该死
You need a loan, you go to the bank.
你需要贷款 就去银行
Oh, who do you think I owe the money to?
哦 你以为我欠的是谁的钱呢
You think they just keep giving you more?
你以为他们会一直给你更多钱吗
Look, I'm telling you I did it right.
听着 我告诉你我做的不错
A clear agreement, I can pay it back
协议明确 我可以还清的
once them cows are ready for the sale.
只要等奶牛能卖了
It don't matter. You go through their office,
没用的 你去了他们的办公室
you sign a bunch of bullshit paperwork.
签了一堆狗屁文件
That's Big Cat's money all the same.
那都是大猫的钱
Goddammit, use your brain.
该死的 动动脑子
I'll tell you what,
我来告诉你
you ain't paid a cent for that cabin.
你没有为那间小屋付一分钱
That might help fill the hole a little bit, don't you think?
那也许能帮忙填补一点空缺 你觉得呢
You gave the devil an inch, Finn.
你把魔鬼招上门了 芬恩
What was I supposed to do?
我还能怎么办呢
You got an extra 100 grand? No, sir.
你还有十万块吗 没有
All right, so don't worry about it.
好了 别担心了
I'll handle it.
我来处理
No, I'll handle it.
不 我来处理
I know how these animals feed.
我知道这些畜牲是怎么咬人的
You need to dry out.
你要清醒清醒
Quit hanging around the house.
别在家里呆着了
Go huntin', take Savannah. She wants to go with you.
打猎去 带上萨凡纳 她想和你一起去
Well, all I'm in the mood to shoot is this bourbon.
我现在只想喝点波旁威士忌
But for you, I'll do it outside.
但为了你 我去外面喝
Here.
看
They're cooking right out in the wide open, man.
他们就在大庭广众之下制毒 伙计
Making pills inside.
在里面做药丸
Yeah, we come back here, four or five guys all armed up,
我们回来 四五个人全副武装
they ain't gonna know what's what for.
他们什么也不知道
In and out of there with every one of them damn pills.
把他们每一颗该死的药片全都抢走
All right, look it. I'm gonna go around the building.
好吧 看 我要绕着这里转一圈
Get a better look.
去看更清楚点
You stay here, keep an eye, okay?
你呆在这儿 看着点 好吗
Reg?
雷杰
There he is! Freeze, asshole!
他在这 不许动 混蛋
Oh, shit.
哦 该死
Hands up! Get 'em up!
举起手来 举起来
Get 'em up!
举起来
Look, I appreciate you got a job to do.
听着 我很感激你帮我做了事
Sir, I know it's important,
先生 我知道这很重要
but Mr. Barkley has a very busy day.
但巴克利先生今天很忙
I'm happy to schedule you a time to come in.
我很乐意为您安排一个过来的时间
Well, you best make it now.
你最好就安排在现在
'Cause, I'm not leaving until I talk to Zeke.
因为 我不会离开的 除非我跟泽克聊过
It's all right, Sue. He's with me.
没事的 苏 他和我一起的
What you up to?
你在忙什么
Just homework.
只是家庭作业
Honey, you're gonna run off to some fancy school
亲爱的 你要去上什么高级学校了
and leave your old man here home alone, ain't you?
把你老爸一个人留在家里 是不是
Right now I'm just trying to pass trig.
现在我只想通过三角学考试
Yeah? Well, let me take a look.
是吗 让我看看
You know, I used to get down
你知道吗 我曾经
with some math back in high school.
高中时学过一些数学
So, Cash.
所以 卡什
Yeah.
嗯
What can I do for you?
我能为你做什么
I'm here to find out
我来看看到底
what Finney owes, so we can take care of it.
芬尼欠了多少钱  我们好还上
I'm sorry, Cash. You seem to be confused.
对不起 卡什 你好像搞错了
I don't think this is even math.
我觉得这根本就不是数学
"Secant..." "Secant..."
余割  余割
Oh, hell, I don't even think that explanation's in English.
哦 见鬼 我甚至不认为这是用英语解答的
Hey, honey, you stay right here.
嘿 亲爱的 你就待在这儿
Uncle Finney, open up!
芬尼叔叔 开门
Who is it?
是谁
I see him!
我看到他了
Okay. Go hide in the back.
好吧 躲到后面去
Hey, he's trying to get out the back!
嘿 他想从后面逃走
Come on, Finn.
来吧 芬恩
You don't wanna make us kick this door in!
你不会想让我们踢开这扇门吧
I'm just trying to figure out
我只是想弄清楚
why you're beating on my door unannounced!
你们为什么不请自来敲我的门
Open this door, Finney.
开门 芬尼
Hey.
嘿
Hey. How you doing, Buck?
嘿 你好吗 巴克
Okay.
好吧
Big Cat just wanted us to pay you a little visit.
大猫只是想让我们来拜访一下你
Said to check up on our investment.
说要查查我们的投资
Oh, yeah, yeah.
哦 是的 是的
Yeah, I'ma... I'ma pull it together.
是的 我 我会凑齐的
I mean, it ain't even due yet, so you know.
我的意思是 都还没有到期 所以你知道
Leave him alone!
放开他
It doesn't look like you're pulling together shit.
你看起来不像在凑他妈的钱啊
- Stop! - Shut that kid up.
- 住手 - 让那孩子闭嘴
Don't you touch her!
别碰她
- Lay off! - Hey, hey, hey.
- 放手 - 嘿
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
哦 嘿 嘿
Damn straight. This here. You are wrong...
该死的 呆在这 你大错特错了
Get him, boys.
抓住他 伙计们
Far as the contract is concerned,
就合同而言
the farm belongs to Big Cat.
农场属于大猫了
Now maybe you can earn it back.
现在 也许你能把它赚回去
But it's not the kind of debt that you can just
但这不是你想还就能还的
walk in and pay.
那种债务
Even if you had the money.
就算你有钱
No, the debt's settled when Big Cat says it's settled.
不 大猫说解决了 债务就解决了
Until then, you don't own the ranch.
在此之前 牧场并不归你们所有
Now, Cash, is there anything else
卡什 还有什么
I can do for you?
我能为你做的么
Hey.
嘿
All right, little darling, I ain't gonna hurt you.
好了 小可爱 我不会伤害你的
I'm sorry.
对不起
Buck... Okay. Okay.
巴克  好了 好了
Look, you shoot me, ain't nobody getting paid.
听着 你打死我 谁也拿不到钱
It's got nothing to do with money.
这与钱无关
What happened?
怎么了
They put a gun to his ears and fired.
他们拿枪对着他的耳朵开了枪
- Finney? - I can't hear shit.
- 芬尼 - 我什么都听不见
Let's get you inside. Come on.
我们进去吧 来吧
Come on.
来吧
I am so sorry. I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉 对不起
- Easy. Just breathe. - I'm so sorry.
- 放轻松 深呼吸 - 真对不起
Just breathe it out.
呼气
Oh.
哦
I cut one of 'em.
我扎了一个
Which one?
哪一个
The one that's always giggling.
总是咯咯笑的那个
The Doe. I'm gonna get this figured out.
杜伊 我会想办法解决的
I need you to look after your dad, okay?
我需要你照顾你爸爸 好吗
I'll be back in a couple of hours.
我几小时后就回来
Okay.
好吧
Mr. Williams?
威廉姆斯先生
Sheriff will see you now.
警长现在要见你
Looky here.
看这里
Finally turning yourself in, Cash?
终于要自首了吗 卡什
Good to see you too, Duke.
我也很高兴见到你 杜克
Cash, come in.
卡什 进来
Always figured I'd have you sitting in a cell.
一直以为我会把你关在牢房里
Not across from my desk.
而不是坐在我办公桌对面
What's this about?
这是怎么回事
I got a Big Cat problem.
我有一只大猫的问题
Now, this ought to be interesting.
现在 这应该会很有趣
Well, Finney went to her for a loan on the farm
芬尼向她借了一笔农场贷款
and she's tightening the screws.
她正在把人逼上绝路
Seems anyone should know better, it's him.
看来应该搞清楚点的人 是他啊
Oh, come on, Sheriff.
得了吧 警长
I mean, she's the damn queen of Odim County.
我是说 她可是奥迪姆郡的女王
That's something you sure as hell had a hand in, Cash.
那个你肯定也有功劳的 卡什
Mm.
嗯
So if you wanna talk about that, we're all ears.
所以 如果你想谈这个 我们洗耳恭听
As far as the loan, I'd say you talk to Zeke.
至于贷款 我建议你去找泽克谈谈
Yeah.
是啊
Yeah. Well, did that.
是啊 是啊 谈过了
Look, we wanna take her down just as bad as you do.
听着 我们和你一样 非常想拿下她
But we need proof of wrongdoing, not just accusations.
但我们需要不法行为的证据 口说无凭
So how about it, Cash?
怎么样 卡什
You got some information?
你有消息吗
If you did, it could solve a lot of problems for both of us.
如果你有 就能为我们俩解决很多问题
I'm just trying to hold on to my sister's place.
我只是想保住我姐姐的地方
Then bring me something concrete I can take to a judge.
那就给我一些具体的 我可以拿去给法官看的东西
Hang my daddy's gun.
挂好我爸爸的枪
Here. Here.
这里 这里
Lazarus, you're gonna have to excuse me.
拉撒路 请原谅我的失陪
I really like your ideas,
我非常喜欢你的想法
but I'm gonna have to ponder them.
但我得好好想想
Yeah, yeah, no problem.
好 好 没问题
What's up, man?
最近怎么样
Cash.
卡什
Wanna tell me why you're putting the screws on me and my family?
想告诉我 你为什么要搞我和我的家人吗
Having your men put their hands on a little girl?
派你的人对一个小女孩动手动脚
You're upset.
你生气了
Shot Finney's ears out in front of Savannah.
在萨凡纳面前打爆芬尼的耳朵
His ears will be ringing for a few days,
他的耳鸣会持续几天
no doubt about that.
这一点毋庸置疑
But the message was for you, Cash.
但这信息是给你的 卡什
You missed it before.
你之前错过了
When I have to send a message a second time,
当我需要第二次发送信息时
it comes with more volume.
音量就会更大了
I don't want your cows or your land.
我不想要你的奶牛和土地
Hell, I didn't wanna give Finney a loan in the first damn place,
该死的 我特么一开始就不想给芬尼贷款
because I knew
因为我知道
the drunken son of a bitch would piss it away.
那个醉醺醺的狗娘养的会把钱撒掉
So here I am doing the honorable thing,
所以 我在这里发个慈悲
giving you the opportunity to work it off,
给你一个机会来抵债
so I don't have to put Finney in a hole
这样我就不用把芬尼埋进
next to your sister, Rachel.
你姐姐瑞秋旁边的墓穴里了
I'm out.
我洗手不干了
We had an agreement.
我们说好了的
I've grown since you left.
你走后 我壮大了不少
It's no longer just plants and pills.
不再只是植物和药片
I'm into empire-building, Cash.
我正在建立帝国 卡什
I got my fingers and hands in everything.
我现在手眼通天势力无边
It's a delicate time in my enterprise.
现在是我事业里的一个微妙的时刻
We're on the verge of something big.
我们即将迎来一件大事
And I could use an extra hand.
我还需要多一个帮手
Now, I got good, strong boys,
现在 我有许多强壮的好手下
raised on my rules and dedicated, every one of 'em,
我的规矩下培养出来的 兢兢业业 无一例外
but they don't have your gifts.
但他们没有你的天赋
You were always so good with people.
你总是那么善于与人打交道
But then you could be a cold-hearted son of a bitch
但你也可以是个冷酷无情的狗娘养的
just as easy.
轻而易举
That's what made you so good.
这就是你如此优秀的原因
I'm not sure what I'm supposed to consider,
我不知道我应该考虑什么
unless you give me some specifics.
除非你告诉我一些具体情况
Three jobs of my choosing.
完成三份由我选出来的工作
That's what it'll take to pay back the debt.
这样就能还清债务
If I decline?
如果我拒绝呢
You can take the silver or you can take the lead.
小心你的选择，选错了可是有后果的
I do this, it's to pay off a debt.
我做这个 只是为了还债
Three jobs and I'm done.
就三份工作 然后我就不干了
Simple and plain.
简单直接
Of course, baby.
当然 宝贝
No need to be complicated.
不需要搞得太复杂
How you doing?
你好吗
Worst goddamn thing
最糟糕的事情
that happened in front of Savannah.
就发生在萨凡纳面前
I don't disagree.
我没意见
Grown man, can't take care of my own land.
大男人 却不能照顾好自己的土地
Couldn't take care of my wife. Now, my little girl.
不能照顾好我妻子 现在 又是我的小女儿
You're not the only one twisting yourself up about things.
你不是唯一一个纠结这些事情的人
No. Maybe I just wasn't cut out to be a father.
不 也许我就是不适合当父亲
Hm.
嗯
You gotta quit talking like that.
你不能再这么说了
That's not helping anyone.
这对任何人都没有帮助
- I know. - Especially Savannah.
- 我知道 - 尤其是萨凡纳
I'm just tired of thinking.
我只是厌倦了胡思乱想
I'm tired of feeling.
我厌倦了这种感觉
Tired of drinking.
厌倦了喝多
Being hungover.
烂醉如泥
I'm so tired of drinking.
我已经厌倦了喝多酒
It's not gonna be easy drawing off.
这可不是件容易戒掉的事
But I'll be there for you, every way I can.
但我会尽我所能支持你的
How much trouble are we in?
我们的麻烦有多大
What can I do?
我能做些什么
Keep reading. Keep studying.
继续阅读 继续学习
So you don't make the same mistakes we have.
这样你就不会重蹈我们的覆辙
Don't talk to me like I don't understand.
别说的好像我不懂
I know you do.
我知道你懂
I can help.
我可以帮忙
I know you can.
我知道你可以
I just want you to stay focused on what matters.
我只想让你专注于重要的事情
That's not some stupid books.
这些愚蠢的书没那么重要
That's dad, you, and the farm.
重要的是爸爸 你和农场
I can't fault you there.
这你倒说的没错
You're right.
你说得对
But we got this worked out, okay?
但我们已经解决了 好吗
There's nothing you can do on this, I promise.
没有什么需要你做的了 我保证
How about we go find your dad?
我们去找你爸爸怎么样
He's got a fire going and everything.
他点了一团篝火 什么都有
I can't promise you s'mores.
但是我不能保证有烤肉
What's your name, son?
你叫什么名字 孩子
Harlen.
哈伦
Harlen. As much pain as you're in right now,
哈伦 就像你现在这样的疼痛
I can promise you it's gonna get a lot, lot worse
我向你保证 会痛得越来越厉害的
if you don't tell me
如果你不告诉我
who you're working with on this thing.
你跟谁一伙来干这事的
Nobody, heard you were making pills out there.
没谁了 听说你在外面做药丸
Figured we'd see if we could get a little for ourselves.
我们就想看看能不能给自己弄一点
That's it.
就是这样
That doesn't sound very sophisticated.
这听起来并不复杂
No.
不
Please, I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
求你了 对不起 不会再发生了
I would like to believe you, but I gotta be sure.
我愿意相信你 但我必须确定
And I can't rightly have you running around...
我不能让你带着这双连着拇指的贼手
with those thumbs attached to those thieving hands.
在四周乱跑
No, wait, no, no, no, no. I won't come back. I swear.
不 等等 不 不 我不会回来了 我发誓
No, no, no, please don't shoot. No, wait, don't shoot.
不 请别开枪 不 等等 别开枪
Please, please, please.
求你了 求你了
- Are you sure? - Just take my thumb.
- 你确定 - 给你我的拇指
That's a good decision.
这是一个很好的决定
No, no.
不 不
Hold on. Okay.
等一下 好的
There you go.
这就对了
Yeah?
喂
Thanks for coming out.
感谢您的光临
Do I have a choice?
我有选择吗
Nope.
没有
Get your fucking ass out of here.
给我滚出去
You trash piece of shit.
你这个垃圾
Hey, give me one of them.
嘿 给我来一根
Where the hell are you, man?
你到底在哪儿
No.
不
Well, hurry the fuck up, they already dropped me.
那就他妈的快点 他们已经把我扔出来了
You're such a dick.
你真是个混蛋
Go see what we're dealing with.
去看看是什么情况
Must've read my mind.
一定是会读心术
Goddammit, Harlen. I told you to be careful.
该死的 哈伦 我告诉过你要小心的
They got Reggie. He's dead.
他们抓住了雷吉 他死了
And she cut my fucking thumb off!
她还把我的拇指切了下来
We hit these motherfuckers back tonight. Huh?
我们今晚就回去搞这些混蛋 啊
Let's go! Get loaded up!
出发吧 上车
Call the boys, Bobby.
打电话给兄弟们 鲍比
All of them. Get fucking ready.
所有的人 他妈的准备好
Five guys. Look like locals.
五个人 看起来像本地人
All strung out.
都在兴头上
Talking about revenge and calling in the boys.
喊着要复仇和叫人
Calling in the boys, huh?
把兄弟们叫来 嗯
Looks like we got us some big-timers.
看来我们碰上了一些大人物
Talk to me. What do we got?
跟我说说 有什么发现
Yeah, it's just like we thought.
是啊 跟我们想的一样
All right, we'll go in the front.
好吧 我们上前面去
Why don't you go in the back, Cash?
你去后面吧 卡什
I'm gonna need a gun.
我需要一把枪
I got your gun.
你的枪在这
Yeah, baby.
是啊 宝贝
Ready, brother?
准备好了吗 兄弟
All right, boys. Move out.
好了 兄弟们 出发
Gimme the fucking gun, asshole.
把枪给我 混蛋
Here you go. There's your gun.
给你 这是你的枪
Motherfuckers.
狗娘养的
Shut the fuck up, man.
闭上你的臭嘴
Here's what we're gonna do, we're gonna...
我们要做的是
There's the son of a bitch. Look at that, Cash got him.
这就是那个狗娘养的 看啊 卡什搞定他了
He almost got him.
他差点就搞定他了
My gun wasn't loaded.
我的枪没子弹
Whoops.
哎呀
Cash, you just passed the shit test.
卡什 你刚刚通过了狗屎测试
Let's get the fuck out of here.
我们走吧
Ah.
啊
All right
好的
Oh.
哦
You're up early.
你起得真早
Goddamn.
该死的
How long you been standing there?
你站在那里多久了
Long enough to know you mean business.
时间长到足以知道你是认真的
- Yeah. - You ready?
- 是啊 - 准备好了吗
I never needed something more in my life.
生平第一次如此确定
Twelve o'clock.
Oh, goddamn.
该死的
I'm shaking like an old man.
我抖得像个老头
Stay focused on the task.
专注于任务
In other words, God.
换句话说 就是上帝
- God. - Family.
- 上帝 - 家庭
- Family. - Survival.
- 家庭 - 生存
Survival.
生存
Damn, I got it.
妈的 我打中了
All right, come on.
好吧 来吧
First things first, gotta remove the skin.
首先要做的 是去皮
Start at the top. Just work your way down.
从头开始 一路向下
Just little cuts. Got it?
别切太深 明白了吗
There you go.
这就对了
Thank you.
谢谢
She's got me hemmed in.
她把我困住了
That's what she does. But you're still sitting there.
她就是干这个的 但你还好好活着
A lot of people in that same situation can't say that.
很多处于同样境况的人都没这么幸运
Remember that kid, Tyler Mack?
还记得那个叫泰勒-麦克的孩子吗
- Yeah, the dealer? - Yeah.
- 是啊 毒贩 - 是的
Barely. I was out by then.
不太记得了 那时我已经出来了
I liked him.
我喜欢他
But he was reckless, you know? Deep into pills.
但他很鲁莽 你知道吗 嗑药嗑得太多
Hey, that hillbilly heroin? Razor-sharp claws.
嘿 那个乡村版海洛因 特别厉害
That was my preferred ticket to oblivion.
那是我想要忘记一切时的首选
Me, Rachel, and Finney we'd all party with Tyler.
我 蕾切尔 还有芬尼 我们和泰勒一起开派对
Get loaded for days.
一连吸几天
At that point, it wasn't even fun.
到了那个时候 这根本就不好玩
In so deep.
陷得太深了
All any of us cared about was getting bent.
我们每个人所关心的就是多吸点
We were all just right there on the edge.
我们都在危险的边缘试探
I could feel it.
我能感觉到
Hmm.
嗯
Then I get the call about my sister's overdose.
然后我接到电话 说我姐姐吸毒过量
Doctor said the pills dampened the electrical signal to her heart.
医生说药片抑制了到她心脏的电信号
Snuffed the spark right out.
直接熄灭了火花
- Hmm. - Hmm.
- 嗯 - 嗯
Spent the next two weeks getting wasted.
接下来的两周都浪费了
Missed my own sister's funeral, I was such a mess.
错过了我亲姐姐的葬礼 我真是一团糟
That's when I knew I needed help.
那时我就知道我需要帮助
Took losing her for me to see that.
失去她之后 我才明白这一点
A lot of people never get on the right track.
很多人从未走上正轨
Is that what I'm doing?
那就是我正在做的吗
You think I don't experience doubt?
你以为我不会自我怀疑吗
You think I'm not struggling?
你以为我不挣扎吗
Cash, you're making progress. That's all any of us can do.
卡什 你在进步 这是我们每个人都能做到的
Don't sell it short.
不要轻言放弃
What was it that drew you out?
是什么把你解救出来的
It's nothing quite so dramatic.
没有那么夸张
I had a revelation. Pure and simple.
我得到了一个启示 简单直接
My eyes were opened like Saul on the road to Damascus.
我的眼睛像大马士革路上的扫罗一样睁开了
Yeah, that's pretty dramatic to me.
是啊 对我来说这也太戏剧化了
Maybe you're right, I guess.
也许你是对的 我想
Hell, we got the scars to prove it.
见鬼 我们有伤疤为证
Yeah?
喂
Okay.
好吧
No, I'll handle it.
不 我来处理
Okay.
好吧
What's the word?
怎么说
Lazarus.
拉撒路
His number's up.
他的号码出来了
Why's that?
为什么会这样
Got some side hustle going. Big Cat don't approve.
搞了些副业 大猫不同意
She wants an example made.
她想杀一儆百
So, he'll be coming with us, but he's not coming back.
所以 他会和我们一起去 但他不会回来了
That's a pretty big change of plans
这计划变化可真大
to be dropping last minute.
到最后一刻才被放弃
It's fucked, man.
完蛋了
He's been working this deal for months.
他已经为这笔交易准备了好几个月了
Could open up a whole lane of East Coast distribution.
这将为东海岸的分销开辟一条新路
But you know Big Cat. She makes the decision.
但你了解大猫 是她做的决定
You gonna be able to handle this?
你能搞定吗
Yeah. Easy, no question.
是啊 很简单 没问题
Just make it clean. Nothing fancy.
只要干净利落 不要太花哨
I got it. Jesus.
我知道了 天啊
Oh, boy.
哦 天哪
Just about jumped out of your damn skin.
就差把你的魂吓出来了
Yeah, thanks, asshole.
是啊 谢谢你 混蛋
All right, my brothers.
好了 我的兄弟们
How's about a little 'cid for this trip? Huh?
这次旅行来点小药丸 怎么样 怎么样
That's how you wanna go into this?
你就想这么干这趟活
Well, I do my best work on a tab.
好吧 我干一件事总是做得最好
Two tabs, that's too much.
两件 就太多了
That's over the top. Ain't that right, Wes?
就过头了 是吧 韦斯
Come on, man. Stop messing around.
来吧 伙计 别闹了
Goddamn, man, y'all need to relax.
该死的 伙计 你们都需要放松
These dudes, they like me.
这些家伙 他们喜欢我
They're gonna get spooked by all your fucking stressor vibes.
他们会被你们这该死的紧张气氛吓坏的
All right, let's roll, baby.
好了 走吧 宝贝
Time to become legends, boys.
是时候搞点大事了 孩子们
Now make a left there, cross that bridge.
在那里左转 过桥
You wanna give us a hand here, Wes?
你想帮我们一把吗 韦斯
Or you gonna keep pacing a hole in the ground?
还是你要继续在那边地上踱来踱去
What's the deal, man?
这是怎么回事
You've been acting fucking weird all day.
你他妈一整天都怪怪的
You run out of Percocet or something?
你的止痛药嗑完了还是怎么回事
Wha...
什么
The fuck did you just do?
你刚才做了什么
He knew something was up.
他发现事情不对劲了
The only thing he knew
他只知道一件事
is you were acting like a goddamn jackass.
就是你表现得像个该死的傻瓜
You said do it clean. I did it clean.
你说要干净利落 我做得很干净
After. Do it clean after.
之后 之后要做得干净利落
It's his deal, isn't it?
这是他的交易 不是吗
His contact.
他的联系人
Shit.
妈的
Yeah, shit.
是啊 妈的
Help me get him in the goddamn van.
帮我把他弄上车
Wanna get off the tarp?
想从油布上下来吗
Are you gonna help me get him in the van?
你要帮我把他弄上车吗
I think I'm gonna fucking puke.
我想我他妈的要吐了
Just get the phone.
接电话吧
It's them. Shit.
是他们 妈的
They're 15 minutes out.
他们15分钟后到
Write back, tell 'em
回信 告诉他们
he can't make it, but his boys will be there.
他不能来 但他的兄弟们会到
It's fucking locked. I can't...
锁屏了 我不能
Here, channel your best Lazarus.
给 装得像拉撒路一点
Right. Okay.
好的 好吧
What happens if they ask about Lazarus?
如果他们问起拉撒路怎么办
When they ask, you let me handle it.
当他们问起时 你就让我来处理
Stay cool and get the deal done. Can you do that?
保持冷静 完成交易 你能做到吗
Yeah.
是啊
All right, here they fucking come.
好了 他们他妈的来了
Everybody has their thing.
每个人都有自己的怪癖
For me, it's one specific one.
对我来说 是特别的一个
My men know what it is and they avoid it at all costs
我的人都知道 他们会不惜一切代价避免它
just to not set me off.
就为了不刺激到我
He doesn't like surprises.
他不喜欢惊喜
So, you can imagine my gut feeling...
所以 你可以想象我的感觉
when I get a text...
当我在我们约好的
10 minutes before our scheduled meeting...
碰面时间之前10分钟才收到短信
informing me that I'll be encountering...
通知我 我将遇到
two faces I do not know.
两张我不认识的脸
Instead of the one that I was expecting.
而不是我期待的那个
Lazarus.
拉撒路
So I ask you...
所以我问你
where is sweet,
甜蜜的爱逗乐的
fun-time Lazarus?
拉撒路哪里去了
And why the fuck isn't he here?
为什么他妈的他不在这里
- Look, there must be some... - He couldn't make it.
- 听着 一定有  - 他来不及了
We're here to handle it for him.
我们是来帮他送货的
It's no more complicated than that.
没什么复杂的
What did Lazarus say in his text?
拉撒路在短信里说的什么来着
"LOL."
大笑
"I'm totally blown out right now."
我现在完全崩溃了
"My guys will be there to cover me."
我的兄弟们会在那里掩护我
See, I know Lazarus.
看 我认识拉撒路
Boy likes to have fun.
小子喜欢开玩笑
That's why he's so pleasant to be around.
这就是为什么他如此讨人喜欢
But this... this is out of character.
但这 这不符合他的性格
We're all a little annoyed and surprised
我们都有点恼火和惊讶
he couldn't make it.
他没赶得上
But if you knew Lazarus like we do, well...
但如果你像我们一样了解拉撒路 那么
it's not so out of character for Mr. Fun-Time.
这也算是爱逗乐先生的性格
Nobody move, or I put you down.
谁都不许动 否则我就把你放倒
Don't you do it.
不要这样做
Well, this is a major surprise.
这真是个大惊喜
There's an explanation,
这是有原因的
but I'm not in a position to give it.
但我没资格告诉你
Now, I'm gonna assume that nobody wants to die
现在 我假设没人想死在
on this fine afternoon.
这个美好的下午
And we sure as shit don't wanna tell Big Cat
我们肯定不想告诉大猫
why this turned into a bloodbath.
为什么这会演变成一场血战
So let's stay focused on the matter at hand.
不如我们还是把注意力集中到手头的生意上吧
Can we do that?
我们能做到吗
If you can't play nice,
如果你不能好好玩
I'll take you out of the equation.
我就会把你剔除出去
Understood?
明白了吗
Yeah, I understand.
是的 我明白
Your product's all there.
你的产品就在那里
We good?
妥了吗
Get the money.
去拿钱
Wayne!
韦恩
All right, kid, let's slow down.
好了 孩子 让我们慢慢来
We can still work this out.
我们仍然可以解决这个问题
Wayne? You hear me, Wayne?
韦恩 听到了吗 韦恩
You motherfuckers!
你们这些混蛋
Would you stop shooting
你能不能别开枪
and just listen to what I have to say?
就听我说几句
Fuck you!
去你妈的
We fired in self-defense.
我们开枪是为了自卫
You know that's true.
你知道这是真的
I need you to be smarter than this.
我需要你比这更聪明
Shit.
妈的
Nope, drop it.
不 扔掉
Do it now or I'll shoot you in the face.
现在就扔 否则我就一枪崩了你
This can play out one of two ways.
这有两条出路
I can kill you
我可以杀了你
and take the money and drugs back to Big Cat
并把钱和毒品带回给大猫
and roll the dice on a busted deal.
冒险完成这个烂交易
Or, and this is my personal favorite,
或者 这是出于我个人的好心
you take the drugs, we take the money,
你拿走毒品 我们拿走钱
just like we planned, you go on living,
就像我们计划好的那样 你继续活着
we go on living. What do you say?
我们也继续活着 你怎么说
Smart kid.
聪明的孩子
Come here.
过来
Okay.
好吧
Actually could have gone a lot worse.
其实情况可能更糟
Get the bag.
去拿包
Do I even wanna know what that is?
我想知道那是什么吗
No.
不
You're in the back.
你上后面
- Are you serious? - Yep.
- 你是认真的吗 - 是的
Get in there and babysit your handiwork.
进去看好你的手艺吧
- You all right? - All right.
- 你还好吗 - 没事了
So, three jobs, huh?
所以 三份工作 是吧
It settles us up.
安顿好我们
That was number two.
这是第二个
That don't sit well with me. Not one bit.
我可不这么认为 一点也不
Yeah.
是啊
Well, it's not fitting too well with me either,
嗯 我也觉得不太合适
so if you got any ideas, I'm all ears.
所以 如果你有任何想法 我洗耳恭听
There she is.
她来了
Hey, honey, how was school?
亲爱的 学校怎么样
Good, I guess.
很好 我想
Everything all right?
一切都还好吗
Another day.
又是一天
Tik tok.
滴答
I'm gonna go inside, so you can finish
我要进屋去了 你们可以把
whatever it is you don't want me to hear.
不想让我听到的事情谈完
I appreciate it, honey.
我很感激 亲爱的
- Be in there in a minute. - Great.
- 马上就到 - 好极了
What if Big Cat don't stick to her word?
如果大猫不守信用怎么办
That's why I got a backup plan.
这就是为什么我有后备计划
There a reason you came ready for war?
有什么原因让你像是打仗来了吗
Is there a reason you invited me out to the middle of nowhere?
你邀请我到这荒郊野外是有原因的吗
I wanna give you Big Cat.
我想把大猫送给你
Oh, yeah?
哦 是吗
How you gonna do that, Cash?
你打算怎么做 卡什
She's got labs all over these hills,
她的实验室遍布这些山丘
all producing.
全在生产
She's trading trucks full of drugs for cash.
她用一卡车一卡车的毒品换取现金
That's just for starters.
这只是开始
That sound like a mighty good story.
听起来是个不错的故事
But I'm gonna need more than a story.
但我需要的不仅仅是一个故事
I need something that's gonna tie her directly
我需要能直接把一切罪行
to everything that's happening. Can you give me that?
都绑在她身上的东西 你能给我吗
You tell me what you want, I'll get it.
你告诉我你想要什么 我就给你
But I don't exist not to anybody.
但不要告诉任何人我的存在
It gets out I'm feeding you...
我只给你一个人消息就行
Big Cat roasts my family on a spit, you understand?
大猫把我的家人放在烤架上烤 你明白吗
I get it.
我明白了
I understand what you need
我知道你需要什么
and what it means to take care of your family.
以及照顾家庭的意义
I got you on that, I give you my word.
我明白你的意思 我向你保证
I could call my buddy down at the DA,
我可以打电话给我在地方检察院的朋友
we get into it and see what we need for a conviction,
我们研究一下 看看我们需要什么来定罪
but I need you to not fuck me on this, Cash.
但我需要你别在这件事上耍我 卡什
I want her gone.
我要她消失
Me too.
我也是
Good.
很好
Pick a better meeting spot next time.
下次选择一个更好的会面地点
Bottom right corner.
右下角
Breathe, relax.
呼吸 放松
Bottom left corner.
左下角
All right, snug in your shoulder, loose hands.
好了 肩膀贴紧 手放松
I can be snug or looser, I can't do both.
我可以紧一点 也可以松一点 但不能同时做到
Well, pull it in with your arms, not your hands.
用胳膊顶着 不要用手
Slow it all down, Savannah.
动作放慢 萨凡纳
It's not about speed, it's process.
这与速度无关 重要的是过程
See it, say the word, squeeze that trigger,
看着 说出那个词 扣动扳机
you know what to do.
你知道该怎么做
For God.
为了上帝
Family.
家庭
Survival.
生存
All right, second ring, good.
好的 第二环 很好
Team effort, there you go.
团队合作 就是这样
Oh.
哦
Oh, are we done?
哦 结束了吗
- Heck no! - That's what I'm talking about.
- 才怪 - 这就是我要说的
Your license and registration, please.
请出示驾照和行驶证
There you go.
这就对了
What's that about?
这是怎么回事
That's gratitude, officer.
这就是心意 警官
It's courtesy from our first lady
这是奥迪姆县第一夫人的
of Odim County.
一点小意思
- It's for you. - What's that, about 100 bucks?
- 给你的 - 多少钱 100块左右
Yes.
是的
Now, that's a handsome sum, right there.
这可是一笔不小的数目
Yeah.
是啊
I'm gonna let you hold on to it.
我会让你留着它的
Oh, you're all right, officer, thank you.
哦 你没事了 警官 谢谢你
I want you to step out of the car.
我要你下车
Are you sure about that?
你确定吗
- One hundred percent. - I don't think
- 百分之百 - 我不认为
that's in your best interest, officer, I... I don't. I...
这对你有什么好处 警官 我  我没有
Well, I want you to step out of the car,
我要你下车
I want you to pop the trunk, so I can do a nice inventory
我想让你打开后备箱 这样我就可以对这辆老车
search of the old girl. I'm gonna go bumper to bumper.
进行一次彻底的清点检查 我要去管理交通了
Yeah, I'm... Now.
是的 我 现在
Woah! Let it fucking go!
哇哦 放他妈的手
Get out the fucking car!
给我他妈下车
It'll be all right.
会没事的
Give me your fucking arm!
把你的胳膊给我
Oh, yeah, you fucked up today.
哦 是的 你今天搞砸了
Oh, yeah.
哦 是的
Now you get to think about what you just tried to do.
现在 你得好好想想你刚才想做什么
Fuck! Fuck you!
操 去你妈的
Fuck!
妈的
Goddamn.
该死的
You just fucked up big-time!
你这回搞大了
Oh, yeah, you got plenty of time to think about this.
哦 是的 你有足够的时间考虑这个问题
I got one of Big Cat's fucking mules
我在路边逮到
on the side of the road.
一头大猫的骡子
Cash, it's Duke. Man, pick up when I'm calling,
卡什 我是杜克 伙计 我打电话的时候记得接
I'm trying to get a hold of you.
我正试着联系你
I talked to my guy at the DA and he says if you can give us
我和检察官谈过了 他说如果你能给我们
these drug labs on a map,
这些毒品实验室的地图
we may be able to put this thing together.
我们也许能把这事解决掉
I'm gonna need you to wear a wire.
我需要你戴上窃听器
You can't hide under a rock on this one.
这事你是躲不掉的
Call me back. Clock ticking.
给我回电话 时间不多了
Time to go, Cash. Get in the car.
该走了 卡什 上车
Where we going?
我们要去哪里
Don't worry about that. You just get in the car.
别担心 你只管上车
I don't get in the car with you.
我不跟你上车
- Why not? - I don't like you.
- 为什么不呢 - 我不喜欢你
Because I think you're an asshole.
因为我觉得你是个混蛋
Well, we don't think much of you, either.
我们也不看好你
So I guess we'll just have to risk it.
所以我想我们只能冒这个险了
Heard there was a real clusterfuck in the woods, huh?
听说树林里发生了一场大混乱
Oh! Oh, you're late! Come on, boys.
你们迟到了 来吧 兄弟们
Big Cat wants everyone around the table.
大猫希望大家都能坐在桌旁
- Zeke. - Cash.
- 泽克 - 卡什
Quiet down.
安静下来
I said quiet down. I got something to say.
我说了安静 我有话要说
I want you to know...
我想让你们知道
that we are growing.
我们正在扩张
And with that, I wanna draw your attention
因此 我想提请大家注意
to my son Zeke.
我的儿子泽克
You did things for my business that I never knew possible.
你为我的业务所做的一切 是我从未想到过的
So I want it noted, in front of all these reprobates...
所以我想当着所有这些后生的面
that I love you and I appreciate you.
我爱你 我感激你
I love you, Mom.
我爱你 妈妈
To my baby boy, Zeke.
敬我的宝贝儿子 泽克
Zeke.
泽克
And now to this pouty-faced son of a bitch...
现在来看看这个满脸横肉的狗娘养的
Cash.
卡什
Worked for me back in the day. Things didn't go so well.
当年跟着我干的 干得不那么顺利
It got kind of ugly.
事情搞得还有点难看
But I don't blame you, Cash.
但我不怪你 卡什
I know I can be a nasty old bitch.
我知道我是个下流的老婊子
But I thought I'd give you another chance to do
但我想再给你一次机会来跟着我干
right by these hills.
就在这些山丘旁边
And boy, did you. Hm?
孩子 你做到了 嗯
You salvaged a deal that in anyone else's hands
你挽救了一笔假如换成其他人
would have been a goat fuck.
早就会被山羊操翻了的交易
But you delivered like you always did.
但你还是一如既往地完成了任务
I got big plans for you.
我为你准备了大计划
I got big plans for all of you.
我为大家准备了大计划
I'm talking greenback dollars.
我说的是美元
- Yeah! - Truckloads
- 是的 - 一卡车
and truckloads of greenback dollars.
和一卡车的美元
Let's drink to fucking truckloads!
让我们为他妈的一卡车干杯
You want out of my crew.
你想离开我的团伙
You take the mark.
你就把纹身拿掉
- Mm. Yeah. You too. - Take care.
- 嗯 你也是 - 保重
All right, you animals, move it into the other room.
好吧 你们这些畜生 换到另一个房间去
Get your asses in here.
都给我滚进来
Are you ready for the entertainment?
你准备好开始娱乐了吗
Oh, shit. Okay, come on, baby.
哦 该死 好了 来吧 宝贝
Let's show the boys who we got
让我们给兄弟们展示一下
joining us this evening.
今晚的嘉宾吧
Now we're talking.
这才像话嘛
There we go.
好了
That's what I'm talking about.
我说的就是这个
You all know Duke.
你们都认识杜克
Yup. Yeah.
是的 是啊
He's our top-notch deputy.
他是我们一流的副警长
Real fan of our work.
我们工作的死忠粉
Probably got your picture up on a cork board.
可能把你们的照片都贴在软木板上了
He's been a real thorn in our side.
他一直是我们的眼中钉
But what Duke here failed to realize
但杜克没有意识到的
is these hills, they talk to me,
是这些山丘 它们在跟我说话
they tell me things,
它们告诉我一些事情
and they're telling me right now to do such
他们现在就叫我对你
savage things to you
下一些野蛮的
that it spreads like wildfire,
会像野火一样蔓延开来的狠手
and don't nobody wanna follow in your footsteps.
然后就没有人再想步你的后尘
Jett, come introduce yourself to the deputy.
杰特 过来跟副警长自我介绍一下
Ooh, Jett.
哦 杰特
Straighten up now, Duke.
坐直了 杜克
And say hello to Odim County's badass brothers.
向奥迪姆县的坏蛋兄弟们问好
Now, I want you boys to get creative.
现在 我要你们发挥创意
Feel free to mix it up.
随意搭配
Yeah.
是啊
Ooh.
哦
I got it all laid out for you.
我都为你们准备好了
- Mm-hmm. - Yeah.
- 嗯 - 是的
- Mm-hmm. - Hmm.
- 嗯 - 嗯
Yeah, buddy.
好啊 伙计
There a problem, officer?
有问题吗 警官
License and registration.
驾照和行驶证
Yeah, we got that.
是的 我们有
Oh.
哦
I don't think I've ever seen knees shatter like that.
我从没见过碎成这样的膝盖
Fuck.
妈的
I wanna see just how badly you wanna live.
我想看看你有多想活下去
So if you beg just right,
所以 如果你求得对路
I might let you crawl out of here.
我可能会让你爬出去
Would you like that opportunity?
你想要这样的机会吗
Hmm.
嗯
Get that thing off him. See what comes.
把他嘴解开  看看有什么要说的
I... I got a son.
我有个儿子
And my son needs me.
我儿子需要我
And I promise you, I swear to God,
我向你保证 我对天发誓
I swear on everything I love, I'll...
我以我所爱的一切起誓 我会
I'll walk away, I'll never say anything
我会走开 我永远不会
to anybody about anything.
对任何人说任何事
I'm begging you, please.
我求你了
That's good for me to hear.
我很高兴听到这个
Please.
求求你
But that's not enough for me. I gotta send a message.
但这对我来说还不够 我得传达一个信息
Please.
求求你
Somebody in here, just fucking help...
谁来帮帮忙
Nope, we're gonna do this right and proper.
不 我们要把这事做的又好又漂亮
No.
不
The only question is...
唯一的问题是
which of these goes where?
这些东西要扎哪
Any suggestions?
有什么建议吗
Seriously? Oh.
真的吗 哦
Come on now, that is some weak sauce.
得了吧 这酱汁太淡了
Cash. You gonna do us the honors?
卡什 你会给我们这个荣幸吗
I think everybody's had enough.
我想大家都受够了
Just let me take him out to the woods,
让我带他去树林里吧
I'll finish him there...
我会在那里解决他
then dispose of what's left.
然后再处理掉剩下的
Y'all reached your limit on this?
你们就这样都到极限了吗
If you're gonna survive in these hills,
如果你想在这些山上生存下去
you need to get used to a little blood.
你需要习惯一点血腥味
Isn't that right, Cash? Eh?
是不是 卡什 啊
Take him out back, feed him to my dogs.
把他带后面去 喂我的狗
Then you can bury what's left.
然后你再把剩下的埋起来
And then I'm done.
然后我就不干了
You're done?
你不干了
Yeah.
是啊
Three jobs.
三份工作
That was the deal.
说好的
It don't matter what you think.
你怎么想并不重要
I say when it's over.
我说结束才结束
And that goes for your niece,
你的侄女
your drunk-ass brother-in-law,
你的酒鬼姐夫 也是一样
and your sister's bones buried at the farm.
你姐姐的遗骨还埋在农场里
You got me, boy?
听懂了吗 孩子
Yeah.
是啊
What?
什么
Yeah. I got it.
好 我知道了
Good.
很好
Now get the fuck out of my sight.
现在给我滚远点
Get me a drink. A whiskey.
给我来一杯 威士忌
Yes, ma'am.
是的 夫人
Hey, hey.
嘿 嘿
You sure as hell know how to push that woman's buttons.
你肯定知道如何刺激那女人的神经
I can't say I've ever seen Big Cat take so much
我从未见过大猫忍了一个人这么多之后
from one person and still be breathing.
还能继续正常呼吸
So...
所以
you better stay put until she lands on a conclusion.
在她答应结束之前 你最好老实点
What?
什么
You're gonna wanna see this.
你会想看看这个的
Had our guy get in that deputy's phone.
让我们的人监听了副警长的电话
Look who he's been talking to.
看看他都在跟谁说话
Get out.
滚出去
How do you want me to handle this?
你想让我怎么处理这件事
Severely.
狠一点
Yes, ma'am.
是的 夫人
Dad, you ready?
爸爸 准备好了吗
Yeah. Yeah, I'll be right out.
好了 我马上出来
Yeah, hey, we about ready.
我们准备好了
Gonna miss this one.
这次我不去了
You do know I ain't been back to that church
你知道我没有回过那座教堂吧
since the funeral.
自从葬礼之后
You got Savannah there.
萨凡纳在那儿
That's enough conviction for the three of us.
对我们三个人来说 信念已经足够了
No doubt about that.
这一点毋庸置疑
What you got going on?
你在干什么
Backup plan went to shit.
备用计划泡汤了
I'm figuring a way to fix it, get some evidence.
我正在想办法解决它 找些证据
- You need some help? - Sure don't.
- 需要帮忙吗 - 当然不需要
I want you and Savannah
我要你和萨凡纳
as far away from this as possible.
离这事越远越好
I gotta go.
我得走了
Hey, Cash. Ca...
嘿 卡什 卡
Whoa.
哇哦
- Hey. - Dad, looking nice.
- 嘿 - 爸爸 看起来不错
Thank you.
谢谢
It's a little dusty, but I think it'll work.
虽然有点灰尘 但我觉得还可以穿
It's fine. It... You look great.
没关系 它 你看起来不错
Oh, thank you. You ready?
谢谢 准备好了吗
- Yeah, I'm ready. - All right.
- 我准备好了 - 好的
Hmm.
嗯
Good morning, everybody.
大家早上好
Good morning.
早上好
Nice to see your beautiful faces.
很高兴看到你们美丽的脸庞
Today, I...
今天 我
I think...
我想
I think today I'm gonna deviate from my planned remarks...
我想今天我会偏离之前计划好的主题
to speak to you from the heart.
跟你们说说心里话
We tend to focus on those sins that bring tangible things
我们倾向于关注那些给我们的生活带来
into our lives, whether it's greed...
实实在在的好处的罪恶  而不管是不是贪婪......
lust, pride.
纵欲 骄傲
Something we don't think about much
我们很少去想
is ridding our lives of those sins
如何在生活中摆脱那些
that have no worldly benefit,
对世俗毫无益处的罪恶
like guilt, self-loathing, anger at God,
比如内疚 自责 对上帝的愤怒
or anger at ourselves.
或对自己的愤怒
These are the things that weigh us down
这些都是拖累我们
and distract us from what's important.
并分散我们对重要事物的注意力的
Honey, I think I gotta step out.
亲爱的 我想我得出去了
God doesn't want you carrying the weight
上帝不想让你背负
- of your sin. - I'll come with you.
- 你的罪孽 - 我和你一起出去
He wants you to be present...
他希望你能
- with those who are with you now.  - I'll be back.
- 与现在和你们同在的人在一起 - 我会回来的
Dedicate yourself to them.
为他们奉献自己
Let them be the benefactors of your love and labor.
让他们成为你的爱和辛劳的滋养
Hey, Dad.
嘿 爸爸
Hey.
嘿
You okay?
你还好吗
I am so sorry, Savannah.
我很抱歉 萨凡纳
It's okay.
没关系
I'm sorry I haven't been a better dad to you.
很抱歉 我没能成为你更好的爸爸
Dad, it's okay.
爸爸 没事的
Losing Mom is...
失去妈妈是
It's just been tough.
只是很艰难
But I promise I'm gonna be a better dad to you.
但我保证 我会成为你更好的父亲
I love you.
我爱你
Come here.
过来
I think Mom would just want us to be okay.
我想妈妈只会希望我们都没事
That she would.
她会的
Apologies, Finn.
对不起 芬恩
I've been sitting on that one for a while.
那些话我已经想了很久了
Might have got a little overanxious.
可能有点操之过急了
Oh, thank you.
哦 谢谢
Oh, I thought it was beautiful.
哦 我觉得很美
- Hmm. It's good to see you. - And you.
- 嗯 很高兴见到你 - 我也是
Maybe this means you'll be coming around
也许这意味着你以后会经常
a little more often.
过来转转
Oh, shit.
哦 该死
I don't know.
我不知道
I just wanna take care of mine right now.
我现在只想照顾好自己
Well, when you're ready, we'll be here.
好吧 等你准备好了 我们就在这里
I appreciate that.
我很感激
Let's go.
我们走吧
How about you say we get us a couple of patty melts?
要不 我们去吃点烤肉奶酪三明治
Yeah, I'm down.
好啊 我没问题
- You are? - Yes.
- 是吗 - 是的
Hey, Finney, where's Cash?
芬尼 卡什在哪
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇哦 哇哦 哇哦
Hey, hey. C'mon, c'mon. Hey! Call the cops.
嘿 嘿 来吧 快报警
Call the cops right now!
马上报警
- Get back! - Hey! Get back. Get back now.
- 退后 - 退后 马上退后
Dad! No!
爸爸 不
- Savannah, run! - Dad!
- 萨凡纳 快跑 - 爸爸
Back up! Everybody, back the fuck up!
退后 大家 都他妈的退后
Run! Run!
快跑 快跑
Back up!
后退
Get the fuck back, old man! Back the fuck up!
他妈的退后 老头 他妈的退后
You're not too old to get shot.
你还不算太老 还能中枪
You're gonna kill him!
你会杀了他的
Stop it!
住手
You're gonna kill him!
你会杀了他的
Come on. Run!
快 快跑
- No! - Go!
- 不 - 走
All right.
好的
It'd be a real thrill to put down a preacher.
放倒一个传教士 那可真是太刺激了
Just take it easy, Doe.
别紧张 杜伊
Let's get out of here!
我们走吧
Now! Come on! Let's go, let's go!
快点 来吧 我们走 我们走
Finney. Finney. Oh, Jesus.
芬尼 芬尼 天啊
Sweet Jesus.
天哪
Is that help coming?
救援会来吗
I'm sorry, he's gone.
对不起 他死了
I'll be right outside if you need me.
如果你需要我 我就在外面
Sheriff, what a nice surprise.
警长 真是个惊喜
This a personal call?
这是私人拜访
Afraid not.
恐怕不是
Finney Thompson was beaten in front of the church today.
芬尼-汤普森今天在教堂前被打了
I heard about that.
我听说了
He's since passed on.
他后来去世了
See, things happen out
你看 事情发生在
in broad daylight in front of people.
光天化日之下 当着众人的面
It's hard for me to control. It makes us both look bad.
让我很难控制 这让我们俩都很难看
Sounds like the boys got carried away.
听起来兄弟们有点失控了
But it is what it is now.
但现在事已至此
I'm saying I need you to make it a little easier on me.
我是说我需要你别让我的日子太难过
People are watching now.
现在大家都在看着呢
You might want to focus
您可能需要多关注关注
on keeping your own house in order.
怎么管好你自己的地盘
I would hate to see any more of your boys
我不想再看到你的手下们
get swallowed up by these hills.
被这些小山吞噬了
Oh, and Lindsey,
哦 还有 林赛
it is a plum job you got...
你的工作真不错
with a lot of perks I provide.
别忘了我提供了很多福利的
A lot of folks would like a nice job like that.
很多人都希望有这样一份好工作
So you stay sharp...
所以你保持警觉一点
'cause there is always somebody waiting behind.
因为总会有人在后面等着的
You have a nice day.
祝你愉快
I should've done something.
我应该做点什么的
I... I should've stopped 'em.
我应该拦住他们的
No.
不
No, sweetie, no.
不 亲爱的 不
There weren't nothing you could do.
至少有一件事情是你可以做到的
Don't ever blame yourself.
就是永远不要责怪自己
Where are the police? We have to tell them who did it.
警察在哪儿 我们得告诉他们是谁干的
They already know.
他们已经知道了
Then why don't they do something?
那他们为什么不做点什么呢
Because these people make everybody afraid.
因为这些人让所有人都害怕
Well, what are we supposed to do then?
那我们该怎么办
We're gonna get you to a safe place.
我们会把你送到安全的地方
Get you to a safe place, okay?
把你送去一个安全的地方 好吗
Oh...
哦
I'm done letting her take from this family.
我不会再让她掠夺这个家了
Pray with me.
和我一起祈祷吧
Pray with me now.
现在就和我一起祈祷吧
I don't think God's gonna like what I have to say.
我想上帝不会喜欢我说的话
Just try.
试试看
Burdens change shoulders when you pray.
当你祈祷时 肩上的重担就会改变
Just speak your truth.
只要说出你的真实想法
Father,
父亲
you took Rachel, and now you've taken Finney.
你带走了瑞秋 现在又带走了芬尼
And I got to be honest...
老实说
I just don't see a plan here.
我看不出这是什么计划
I don't see how a loving God could take my family
我不明白慈爱的上帝怎么会带走我的家人
and leave that little girl with no mom and dad.
让那个小女孩失去父母
It don't make no sense.
没道理啊
In fact, as long as we're being honest here,
事实上 只要我们在这里实话实说
I wonder if you're there at all, if you've abandoned us all
我不知道你是否还在那里 是否已将我们遗弃
in this hell to suffer.
在这个地狱里受苦
Wilder tells me you are there.
维尔德告诉我你在那儿
And that you test your servants.
你要考验你的仆人
Hmm.
嗯
And that this is my burden.
这是我的负担
So I'm gonna do what feels right.
所以我要做感觉正确的事
And I'm gonna trust that, because my blood is on fire.
我相信这一点 因为我现在热血沸腾
But I ask you, Father,
但我请求你 神父
I ask that you protect
我请求你保护
what's left of my family while I go about this.
我其余的家人 在我做这件事的同时
I ask that you give me the courage,
我请求您给我勇气
and the strength, and resolve...
以及力量和决心
to kill these bastards.
来杀了这些混蛋
In your name, Father. Amen.
以你的名义 父啊  阿门
Amen.
阿门
Man, you gotta get a new place.
伙计 你得换个地方了
You don't actually bring girls back to this thing.
你不可能真的带女孩回这里来的
Less than I'd like, but yeah.
虽然比我想的少 但还是有的
And it's resulted in fucking?
睡到手的有几个呢
More than you think.
比你想象的还要多
Bullshit, give me that.
胡扯 给我
Here you go.
给你
- Take that. - Later, bro.
- 拿着 - 再见 兄弟
Fuck!
妈的
Didn't know you was trailing, you little fucker.
不知道你在跟踪 小混蛋
Let's go, Cash! You fucking cunt!
我们走 卡什 你个臭婊子
Fucking keys. Fuck.
该死的钥匙 妈的
Found the family's truck in the woods.
在树林里找到了他们家的卡车
Even left his damn keys.
甚至还留下了该死的钥匙
We'll be taking care of this in-house.
我们会内部解决这个问题
Anything you'd like me to do?
有什么需要我做的吗
Keep this mess from getting out.
别让这个烂摊子传出去
Will do.
好的
You boys.
你们啊
You spiraled so far into the depths
堕落到了如此地步
of depravity that you abandoned all
放弃了所有约定俗成的
agreed-upon, basic courtesies, even knocking.
最基本的礼貌 连敲门都不愿意了
Girl must have a healthy appetite.
女孩的胃口一定很好
Oh, nope.
哦 不
Old Rusty. Loves a big piece of meat.
老狗拉斯蒂 喜欢大块的肉
Yeah. There's a boy.
是啊 这有个孩子
We're past time for messing around, Pastor.
别跟我们胡搅蛮缠了 牧师
Where is she?
她在哪里
I told you, she ain't here.
我告诉过你 她不在这里
I do take issue, however, with the murder of her father.
不过 我对她父亲被杀一事  确实有点意见
No one gives a damn about your issue...
没人在乎你的意见
I'm gonna ask one last time. Where's the girl?
我再问最后一次 那个女孩在哪儿
Well, I'm telling ya...
好吧 我告诉你
I'm right here. Now leave him alone.
我就在这儿 现在把他放了
No!
不
Smart girl. She just saved your life.
聪明的女孩 她刚刚救了你的命
Now you tell Cash,
现在你去告诉卡什
Big Cat's willing to make a straight trade.
大猫愿意做个交易
His life for the girl's.
他的命换女孩的命
What the hell happened?
到底发生了什么
You didn't answer my calls.
你不接我电话
My phone died. Where's Savannah?
我的手机没电了 萨凡纳呢
They took her from me. I'm sorry.
他们把她从我这抢走了 对不起
They wanna do a straight swap. Your life for her life.
他们想做个交换 用你的命换她的命
I have myself a plan.
我给自己做了个计划
You being here might change it.
你在这里可能会改变它的
No.
不
I think you and I got the same idea.
我想你和我的想法是一样的
Wanna get cleaned up?
想洗洗干净吗
Might splash some water on my face.
可能要洗把脸
Rather take a clean shirt, but...
也想换一件干净的衬衫 但
I like to get filthy when I maul.
我喜欢在干活的时候穿脏衣服
The most important decision of your life are right now.
你一生中最重要的决定就是现在
Don't fuck it up.
别搞砸了
I ain't gonna do nothing.
我什么都不会做
Well, then do nothing while you're putting
好吧 那就什么都不做
your hands behind your back.
双手放在背后
Sit!
坐下
- What the fuck are you doing? - Get your ass up.
- 你们他妈的干什么 - 给我起来
Zeke, we're taking you to lunch.
泽克 我们带你去吃午饭
You don't know what the fuck you're doing!
你们根本不知道自己他妈的惹了什么祸
Sit.
坐下
You motherfuckers!
你们这些混蛋
- Stay. Good boys. - You're fucking dead! No!
- 别动 好孩子 - 你们死定了 不
No!
不
Don't just stand there, Susan, fucking call somebody!
苏珊 别傻站着 快打电话叫人来
Don't do anything, Susan!
什么都别做 苏珊
Fuck!
妈的
I never had a daughter.
我从未有过女儿
I've had three sons, but the hills took two of 'em.
我有三个儿子 但其中两个死在了山里
There was an incident at the law firm.
律师事务所发生了一件事
They got Zeke.
他们抓走了泽克
Zeke's phone. Huh.
泽克的手机 哈
Where's my boy, Cash?
我儿子呢 卡什
Well, he's anxious to get back under your wing.
他迫不及待地想回到你的羽翼之下
Let's do a trade.
我们来做个交易吧
Trade?
交易
Zeke for Savannah.
泽克换萨凡纳
We meet at the rock plant, Avenue 280.
我们在 280 号大道的岩石工厂集合
Here's how this is gonna work.
我来告诉你这要怎么解决
You be at my place. Four o'clock with Zeke.
你来我家 四点钟和泽克一起
You don't show, I'll put another member
你不出现 我就把你另一个家人
of your family in the ground.
埋进地下
That doesn't work for you?
这对你行不通
We each dispose of our wares. Save us both some trouble.
那我们就各自处理掉自己的人质 给我们俩都省点麻烦
Is that clear?
清楚了吗
Four p.m.
下午四点
How'd that go?
进展如何
Change of plan.
改变计划
- Well, that sounds encouraging. - Mm-hmm.
- 听起来不错 - 嗯
Yeah, you're fucked.
是啊 你们完蛋了
I'm real tired of your family.
我真的受够了你们一家
Keep your eye on that little bitch.
盯着那个小贱人
Yes, ma'am.
是的 夫人
♪ I got the Holy Ghost fire... ♪
我得到了圣灵之火
You fucking son of a bitch!
你个狗娘养的
You've signed your fucking death warrant, you motherfucker!
你他妈的死定了 你个混蛋
You're fucking dog shit.
你他妈就是一坨狗屎
You're fucking dead.
你他妈的死定了
♪ Got a Holy Ghost fire
得到了圣灵之火
♪ Got it rolling down The streets ♪
在街道上滚滚向前
No! Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
不 别开枪 别开枪
Fuck!
妈的
Anybody put a shot in my son
谁要是打中我儿子
and you will be on the receiving end.
就等着自作自受吧
It's all right, baby, I'm here.
没事的 宝贝 有我在
Big Cat!
大猫
Hey, Wilder.
嘿 瓦尔德
You got all mixed up in this.
你把一切都搞混了
Where's Cash?
卡什在哪里
Things will go smoother if you and me make this trade.
如果你和我来做这笔交易 事情会更顺利
Keep emotions out of it.
不会感情用事
You come driving up with my son as a hood ornament.
你开车过来 拿我儿子当引擎盖装饰品
I thought you was reformed, preacher.
我以为你已经改过自新了 牧师
I'm more the Old Testament type. Eye for eye, tooth for tooth.
我更像旧约里的那种 以眼还眼 以牙还牙
Hell, now you're speaking my language.
见鬼，现在你说的是我能理解的语言
Let my boy down.
把我的孩子放下来
I don't like seeing him up there like that.
我不喜欢看到他那样躺在那里
We can make the exchange at the same time.
我们可以同时交换人质
I ain't cutting him loose till I got Savannah.
在我接走萨凡纳之前 我是不会放了他的
And I know you ain't tailing me.
我知道你不会跟踪我
If that happens, I'll drop him down the road.
如果发生这种情况 我就把他扔到路上
Sounds good by me.
听起来不错
Go get her.
把她带过来
When Zeke's clear, take him out.
等泽克安全了 就干掉他
We're gonna stuff and mount these motherfuckers.
我们要把这群混蛋塞进去挂起来
Make a show of it.
以儆效尤
Easy now, little girl. Okay?
放松点 小姑娘 好吗
Put the gun down. Put the fucking gun down.
把枪放下  把枪放下
Shit.
妈的
Put him down.
把他放倒
Don't fucking shoot.
别他妈开枪
He's behind the car!
他在车后面
Get a flank on him.
从侧面攻击他
Shit.
妈的
Put a pinch on him.
给他一枪
Goddamn it, Zeke, get out of there!
该死 泽克 快过来
Zeke!
泽克
Zeke, get the hell out of there!
泽克 离开那里
Stay! Stay!
待着 待着
Easy, boy.
别紧张 孩子
Get the fuck back.
滚回去
Zeke!
泽克
Hate to tell you this, Savannah,
真不想告诉你 萨凡纳
but that M1 only holds eight rounds.
但 M1 只能装八发子弹
Know how many you got left?
知道你还剩几颗吗
'Cause I do.
因为我知道
Damn, kid!
该死的 孩子
All right, game over.
好了 游戏结束
I'm gonna take your fucking face off.
我要把你的脸轰烂
Shit.
妈的
End of the line, little girl.
到此为止了吧 小姑娘
No, goddamn you!
不 该死的
Zeke.
泽克
Oh God, Zeke, oh, baby.
哦 上帝 泽克 哦 宝贝
Oh, baby.
哦 宝贝
Oh, God. I'm sorry.
哦 天啊 对不起
Okay.
好吧
God damn you.
真该死
Uncle Cash!
卡什叔叔
Come here. Shh. You okay? Yeah?
过来 嘘 还好吗
Go!
走
Uncle Cash!
卡什叔叔
What do I do?
我该怎么办
Out that window. Keep going. Get out of town.
从窗户出去 一直走 离开小镇
Get out of the whole goddamn state.
滚出这个该死的州
- No! - Savannah. Look at me.
- 不 - 萨凡纳 看着我
For God, for family, and survival. Go.
为了上帝 为了家人 为了生存 走吧
Go now!
现在就走
现在就去
Savannah, go!
萨凡纳 走
Get the hell out!
赶紧出去
You better know there's no place on this earth I won't find her.
你最好知道这世上没有我找不到的地方
I'll see you in hell.
地狱见
My sk...
我
Good morning, everybody.
大家早上好
Good morning.
早上好
I missed you.
我想你们了
It's great to see all your bright, shining faces.
很高兴看到你们一张张灿烂的笑脸
As you know, I haven't been here for a few months.
如你所知 我有几个月没来这里了
I cut myself shaving.
我刮胡子的时候割伤了
- Want something to eat? - You bet.
- 想吃点什么吗 - 当然
Oh, how I have longed to be here with you.
哦 我是多么渴望和你们在一起
Continue our talks
继续我们
about the Lord's word and the Lord's will.
关于主的话语和主的旨意的交流
Today's lesson is on divine vengeance.
今天的课程是关于神圣的复仇的
"What if the breath
"如果点燃
that kindled those grim fires, awaked,
这些阴暗火焰的气息被唤醒
should blow them into sevenfold rage
将它们吹成七倍的怒火
and plunge us into flames?"
让我们陷入火海 "
"Or from above, should intermitted vengeance
或者从高空落下的复仇之手
arm again his red right hand to plague us."
再次伸向我们
How's she doing?
她怎么样了
Good.
很好
Little giddy, huh?
有点晕眩 是吧
《复 仇 之 手》
字幕:Dex7er  公众号:值得看的
♪ Can't keep quiet Through the night ♪
♪ Praying for the dawn sky
♪ Waiting for the day
♪ When the darkness fades away ♪
♪ Fires burning deep within ♪
♪ Smokescreen's got me Lost again ♪
♪ But I've smoldered Long enough ♪
♪ And the ash is piling up ♪
♪ I've been sleeping On my roof ♪
♪ Got a jackknife in my boot ♪
♪ But the red eye
Is still in me ♪
♪ And I've got to find
My way through the dark ♪
♪ Through the darkness I can see ♪
♪ A road that's bound
To set me free ♪
♪ The tunnel's holding on
♪ Can't turn back I'm moving on ♪
♪ Piece of me I left behind
♪ Another piece I try to hide
♪ I'll learn the lines
I'll play the part ♪
♪ I've got to find
my way Through the dark ♪
♪ Through the dark
♪ The rivers that I've crossed ♪
♪ Are as deep
as they are wide ♪
♪ But not enough to wash away
♪ The knots that we have tied
♪ I've lost the
light Along the way ♪
♪ There's just no way Around it ♪
♪ I'll call you
When I've found it ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
♪ As the plane Was touching down ♪
♪ I was thinkin' 'bout
Some old ghost town ♪
♪ The place we used to live ♪
♪ I'll forget,
I won't forgive ♪
♪ Now the fire deep inside ♪
♪ It's burning Right before my eyes ♪
♪ Eradicating the dark
♪ Sometimes all you
need Is a spark ♪
♪ All you need is a spark
♪ The rivers that I've crossed Are
as deep as they are wide ♪
♪ But not enough to wash away
♪ The knots that we have tied
♪ I've lost the
light Along the way ♪
♪ There's just No way around it ♪
♪ I'll call you
when I've found it ♪
♪ I'll call you when
♪ I've found it
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
♪ All you need is a spark